Godwin K. Woo

Phone: (778) 803-5973 E-mail: godwinwoo@gmail.com

Full Stack Web3 Developer with React, Solidity, Python, C#, Object Oriented Design

EDUCATION

MSc Machine Learning, University of British Columbia, 2019

BSc Computer Science, University of British Columbia, 2003

BA Economics & Finance, University of British Columbia, 2001

SKILLS

React Typescript EthersJS Solidity Ganache Truffle Hardhat Web3 Python C# SQL Blockchain VSCode Github

CAREER SUMMARY

Masters in Experimental Medicine specializing in Big Data Machine Learning with 10+ years of software development experience in Financial Industry. Focused, detail-oriented, and curious learner with extensive experience in developing Web3 and C# applications. Looking to join a team where I can apply my experience and continue to grow my skillsets.

WORK EXPERIENCE

DeepCOP Solutions

Web3 Team Lead | Vancouver, BC | Jul 2020 - Present

- Managed web3 developers to create a blockchain social media platform
- Wrote scripts to automatic update testnet prices based on Uniswap mainnet prices
- Wrote deployment scripts for solidity contracts
- Ganache and Hardhat integration

GammaSwap Labs

Blockchain Developer | Fort Meyers, FL | Mar 2022 - Apr 2023

- Delivered testnet app to secure \$1.7m initial round funding.
- Managed and sourced team of 6 developers.
- Set up initial MVC architectural layout. (React, typescript, tailwinds)
- Set up deployment process for local windows and remote linux app hosting.
- Set up CI integration for project repositories.
- Managed manual testing and added automated tests.
- Implementing code review and security practices.
- Maintaining repositories to keep industry practices.
- Maintained contract, readme, and whitepaper documentation.
- · Hands on development with core app feature and tailwinds styling.

UBS Investment Bank

C# and HTML5 Software Developer | New York, NY | Oct 2010 - Aug 2017

NEO Transactional Cost Analysis Post Trade Analytic Web Reporting

- Maintained and developed new features into HTML5 Web app and associated restful services
- Worked closely with product managers to understand requirements.
- Troubleshooting and production support of NEO applications in the Equities space
- Worked with a global team in HK, Singapore, UK and Poland.

Order Management System GUI: C# Winforms UBS Global Equities trading platform

- Designed and implemented variable decimal place display and color on grid data.
- Implemented features to accommodate exchange compliance changes such as Limit Up Limit Down and Mini Options.
- Wrote automated nunit test cases using setups, teardowns, and mock objects.
- Implemented enhancements such as personal options limits, lifetime volume info, default portfolio order settings, and portfolio order confirmation screens.
- Plan and execute roadmaps to resolve larger complex changes.
- Upgraded annually expiring certificates to match webservices.
- · Conducted peer code reviews.
- Led, investigated, documented and resolved existing issues to meet quarterly releases.

KPMG LLP

C#.NET Software Developer | Montvale, NJ | May 2005 - Sep 2010

eWorkPapers: C# Winforms Corporate and Partnership Tax Form preparation tool

- Designed and implemented tax worksheets, signoff, and finalization functionalities.
- Implemented new WCF data contracts and service contracts for new taxforms.
- Designed and developed ETL conversion framework that migrates data from an older implementation of a tax form to the new condensed implementation.
- Managed 4 offshore developers work for the project.
- Designed a Signoff module that facilitates signing of individual worksheets.
- Held code design reviews for complex features.